A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (A-K) FA1783
Rockefeller Archive Center
John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (A-K), Accession 2021:050
1999-2019
Rockefeller Archive Center
John S. and James L. Knight Foundation
FA1783
26.22 Cubic Feet 69 letter document boxes
7.18 Gigabytes 3 optical disks
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains grant records (A-K) for Knight communities (Miami, Philadelphia, Detroit, San Jose, Charlotte, Akron, Macon, St. Paul, Columbus, Grand Forks, and Milledgeville) with a focus on Knight grant program areas including Community and National initiatives, Journalism and Media Innovation, Art, Technology, Learning and Impact, and Trustee-Advised grants. Most grant records include information about the purpose of the grant, the amount gifted, and a final report (where applicable). Each grant has its own grant number which usually represents the year the grant application was filed followed by a unique identifier.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in series according to various Knight program areas:
Series 1: Community and National Initiatives
Series 2: Journalism and Media Innovation
Series 3: Arts
Series 4: Technology and Media Innovation
Series 5: Learning and Impact
Series 6: Other
Series 6.1: Trustee-Advised Grant Program
Series 6.2: Emergency/Impact Fund
Series 6.3: Communication
Series 6.4: Membership
San Jose (Calif.); Miami (Fla.); Social media; Akron (Ohio); Journalism; Charlotte (N.C.); Macon (Ga.); Tallahassee (Fla.); Art; Campaigns, Election -- News media coverage; Voting
- Community and National Initiatives, 1999-2019; 1; 25.44 Cubic Feet 67 letter document boxes
  Scope and Contents
  The Community and National Initiatives program focuses on enhancing local communities by attracting talent, encouraging economic opportunities, and promoting community engagement. This series also contains grants that fall under the Knight Cities Challenge in which grants awarded under this challenge benefit one of the 26 Knight communities and focus on talent, opportunity, or engagement.
  - 8-80 Cities - Guadalajara Study Tour (2017-54126) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Open in 2027
  - 8-80 Cities - 2018 Emerging Cities Champions fellowship program (2017-55260), 2017-2019 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Restricted - Open in 2029
  - 8-80 Cities - Nurture Civic Innovators (2016-52234) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Restricted - Open in 2026
  - 8-80 Cities - Convening and Study Tours (2014-49956), 2014-2016 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 8-80 Cities - Educational Tour (2014-49562) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 500 Startups Incubator - 500 Startups, Miami (2017-53856), 2014-2017 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 500 Startups Incubator - PreMoney Miami (2015-50433) (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Restricted - Open in 2025
  - 500 Startups Incubator - Miami Growth Program (2015-51106) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 500 Startups Incubator - PreMoney Conference, Miami (2014-49930), 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 5000 Role Models of Excellence Foundation - Educational Leadership Training Tour to Washington, D.C. (2013-46639), 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Al-Bustan Seeds of Culture - Tabadul: [Re]Presenting and [Ex]Changing Our America: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54427), 2017-2018 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Restricted - Open in 2028
  - Aberdeen Area Community Foundation - The A Place: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54189), 2017-2018 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Accelerated Growth Partners - Expansion (2016-53416), 2016-2018 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Accelerated Growth Partners - Executive VC Training (2015-50931), 2015-2017 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Accelerated Growth Partners - General Support and Expansion (2014-48522), 2014-2016 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Accelerated Growth Partners - Family Office - Early Stage Education (2014-49876), 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Akron Community Foundation - On the Table Akron (2017-53763) (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Akron Community Service Center and Urban League - Ice House Entrepreneurship Program (2014-49302), 2015 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Akron Development Corporation - Economic Development Plan for Akron (2017-54619), 2017-2018 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Akron Neighborhood Trust - Civic Engagement and Positive Human Relations (2011-0116), 2010-2013 (Box 3, Folder 46-47)
  - Akron SCORE, Chapter 81 - Increase Organizational Capacity and Provide Technical Assistance to Developing Businesses in Summit County (2004-0144), 2004-2007 (Box 4, Folder 49-50)
  - Alexander Mitchell Public Library, Aberdeen - Improve Access to Internet and Computer Technology (2009-2433) (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Amalgam Comics and Coffeehouse, Inc. - Up Up and Away: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54181), 2017-2018 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - American Architectural Foundation, Inc. - National Summit on Design and Urban Mobility (2017-53968) (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Americas Business Council Foundation - Continuity Forum, New World Center Miami (2013-47124), 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research - Survey on the American Project (2017-55073), 2015-2017 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    Survey to examine how place, educational attainment, employment sector, family structure, and demographics influence attitudes toward economic mobility, civic engagement, and trust in institutions.
  - American Friends of Un Techo Para Mi Pais, Inc. - "Colecta" Event to Fight Poverty in Latin America (2014-49473), 2011-2014 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - American Friends of Un Techo Para Mi Pais, Inc. - Second "Colecta" Event to Fight Poverty in Latin America (2014-49473) (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - American Friends of Un Techo Para Mi Pais, Inc. - Clinton Global Initiative Membership, 2012 Annual Meeting Attendance (2012-3537), 2012-2013 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - American Jewish Community - Project Interchange Seminar in Israel for Miami High Tech Entrepreneurs (2017-53755), 2017-2018 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - American Jewish Community - Project Interchange Seminar in Israel for Miami High Tech Entrepreneurs (2015-51596), 2015-2016 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - American Jewish Community - Project Interchange Seminar in Israel for Miami High Tech Entrepreneurs (2014-49463), 2014-2015 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - American Leadership Forum, Silicon Valley Chapter - Urbanism Innovation Network (2014-48360), 2013-2018 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - American Library Association - 2015 National Convention Workshop for Community Engagement (2015-51066) (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - American Statistical Association - Data Exposition Cash Prizes (2012-2142), 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - American Business Council Foundation - 2014 Continuity Forum, Miami (2014-49791), 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - AmericaWalks - Second National Walking Summit, Washington, D.C. (2015-50865) (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Armando Minjarez, Wichita Community Foundation - Horizontes: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54395) (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Art x Love, LLC - @Play: A Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54194), 2014-2017 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Art Sanctuary - Hip H'Opera (2012-0067), 2011-2014 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Ashoka - Ashoka Youth Venture (2013-43020), 2010-2013 (Box 9, Folder 127)
  - The Atlantic Monthly Group, Inc. - CityLab 2016 (2016-52541), 2013-2016 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - The Atlantic Monthly Group, Inc. - Start-Up City: Miami (2013-45878), 2013-2014 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Awesome Foundation Miami LLC - Launch of Foundation (2013-45557), 2011-2013 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Babson College - Women Innovating Now (WIN) (2015-50900), 2013-2017 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Baltimore Community Foundation - 2017 Knight Community Information Lab (KCIL) Winner (2017-54678) (Box 11, Folder 158)
  - Benevolent, NFP - Community Engagement (2013-47904), 2012-2015 (Box 11, Folder 165)
  - Better Block Foundation - League of Creative Interventionist Fellows (2017-53862) (Box 11, Folder 167)
  - Better Block Foundation - Better Block Akron (2017-54081) (Box 12, Folder 168)
  - Better Block Foundation - Inclusive City-Building Lab with Jay Pitter (2017-55061) (Box 12, Folder 169)
  - Better Block Foundation - International Hostel on Airbnb (2015-50675), 2017 (Box 12, Folder 170)
  - Better Block Foundation - Hunter Franks (2016-52110) (Box 12, Folder 172)
  - Better Block Foundation - Akron Study Tour (2016-53163) (Box 12, Folder 173)
  - Better Block Foundation - General Operating Support (2015-51767), 2015-2017 (Box 12, Folder 174)
  - Big Brothers Big Sisters of Greater Miami - Knight YOUmedia Learning Center (2015-51334), 2013-2017 (Box 12, Folder 176)
  - Bill, Hillary, and Chelsea Clinton Foundation - CGI U 2015, University of Miami (2014-49336), 2012-2015 (Box 12, Folder 178)
  - BioInnovation Institute in Akron - Austen Bioinnovation Institution in Akron (ABIA) (2014-48989), 2014-2015 (Box 12, Folder 179)
  - BioInnovation Institute - Knight Research and Education Collaborative in Akron (2008-0119), 2008-2013 (Box 13, Folder 180-184)
  - Blacks in Technology, Twin Cities - 2017Code Switch: Hack for Change (2017-54603) (Box 14, Folder 190)
  - Blue Grass Community Foundation - On the Table, Lexington (2017-53753) (Box 14, Folder 191)
  - Blue Grass Community Foundation - University Cities Conference (2017-55125) (Box 14, Folder 192)
  - Blue Grass Community Foundation - GoodGiving Guide Challenge (2015-50739) (Box 14, Folder 193)
  - Blue Grass Community Foundation - Knight Community Information Challenge (2013-46519), 2011-2013 (Box 14, Folder 194)
    To create a corps of diverse leaders and provide them with journalism and media production training to create local stories of community change.
  - Blue Grass Community Foundation - Online Giving Technologies (2013-46759), 2011-2014 (Box 14, Folder 195)
  - Blue Grass Community Foundation - Online Giving Technologies (2012-0332), 2013 (Box 14, Folder 196)
  - Blue Grass Community Foundation - Supplemental Grant (2009-0264), 2009-2013 (Box 14, Folder 197-198)
  - Blue Grass Community Foundation - Reimagining Lexington's Public Square (2017-55239) (Box 15, Folder 199)
  - BMe (Black Male Engagement) Community - BMe Akron (2017-54559) (Box 15, Folder 200)
  - BMe (Black Male Engagement) Community - Akron Pilot (2016-52450) (Box 15, Folder 201)
    To fund a BMe Community Manager and provide grants to black men in Akron who have shared their stories and are engaging others in strengthening their city.
  - BMe (Black Male Engagement) Community - Black Male Engagement Fund (2013-45602), 2011-2013 (Box 15, Folder 202)
  - BMe (Black Male Engagement) Community - BMe Networks (2013-45663), 2011-2016 (Box 15, Folder 203)
  - Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University - Ready4k: A Text-Message Parenting Program to Support Strong Home-Learning Environments (2016-52807) (Box 15, Folder 209)
  - The Boston Foundation - Learning Lab Forum, Knight Community Information Challenge (2013-46572), 2011-2014 (Box 16, Folder 215)
  - Boys and Girls Clubs of Central Georgia - STEM Lab (2015-51539), 2016 (Box 16, Folder 220)
  - Band Camp University - Rebranding Neighborhoods to Revitalize Detroit (2015-50672), 2013-2016 (Box 16, Folder 226)
  - Breakthrough Miami, Inc. - Academic Enrichment Program for Students from Underserved Communities (2013-45025), 2011-2013 (Box 16, Folder 228)
  - Brian Davis - Cuyahoga Explore-A-Foot: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52484), 2014-2016 (Box 17, Folder 230)
  - Bridge of Grace, Inc. - Tired-A-Lot: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52499), 2014-2016 (Box 17, Folder 231)
  - Brooklyn Community Foundation - Brooklyn Bureau, Knight Community Information Challenge (2011-0123), 2009-2013 (Box 17, Folder 235)
  - Building Community Value - Better Buildings, Better Blocks: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenege Winner (2017-54208) (Box 18, Folder 240)
  - Business Volunteers Unlimited - Young Professional Leader Corps (2016-52941), 2016-2017 (Box 18, Folder 241)
  - Bus Federation Civic Fund - Rep(resentative) MIA; A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54180) (Box 18, Folder 242)
  - C Squared Networks Ltd. - Media Innovation Battlefield (2014-48113), 2014-2015 (Box 18, Folder 243)
  - California Community Foundation - Media Summit on Engaging Immigrant Communities (2017-54783) (Box 18, Folder 244)
  - California Walks - Walk San Jose (2017-55144) (Box 18, Folder 245)
  - Campus Philly - Sustainable Funding Model (2015-51070) (Box 18, Folder 248)
  - Catholic Charities Legal Services Archdiocese of Miami, Inc. - CitzenshipWorks Center (2013-46878), 2010-2015 (Box 19, Folder 256)
  - CCCP Community Trust - Building Community: People, Places, and Partners (2017-53780) (Box 19, Folder 260)
  - CCCP Community Trust - Rail Trail Grove and Field: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54421) (Box 19, Folder 261)
  - CCCP Community Trust - Pedal to Porch / QC Joyrides (2017-55131) (Box 19, Folder 262)
  - CCCP Community Trust - West Side (Charlotte) Business Development (2015-50887), 2012-2017 (Box 19, Folder 263)
  - Center City District Foundation - The Independent Economy in Philadelphia, Charlotte, and Milwaukee (2014-49355), 2013-2014 (Box 19, Folder 265)
  - Center for Active Design, Inc. - Community Life Guidelines (2015-51320), 2015-2017 (Box 19, Folder 266)
  - Center for Active Design, Inc. - Design Guidelines for Robust Engagement (2014-49294), 2012-2014 (Box 19, Folder 267)
  - Center for Applied Transect Studies, Inc. - Project for Learn Urbanism (2013-47351), 2012-2016 (Box 19, Folder 269)
  - Center for Land Reform, Inc. - Beyond Bright: Media Bootcamp (2015-50721), 2013-2015 (Box 20, Folder 271)
  - The Center for Michigan, Inc. - Detroit Participation in Statewide Public Engagement Campaign (2016-52960) (Box 20, Folder 272)
  - Center for Neighborhood Technology - Blueprint for Prosperity (2015-50556) (Box 20, Folder 276)
  - Central Carolina Community Foundation, Inc. - Supplemental Grant to Donor-Advised Fund (2009-0257), 2009-2016 (Box 20, Folder 279)
  - Central Roxborough Civic Association - Neighborhood Conservation Kit (2015-50666) (Box 20, Folder 281)
  - Centre County Community Foundation - Community Collaborative Ice Luminary Project: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52520) (Box 20, Folder 282)
  - Centre County Community Foundation - Centre Gives Giving Day (2015-50778) (Box 20, Folder 283)
  - Centre County Community Foundation - Giving Day Initiative - State College (2013-47096), 2011-2013 (Box 20, Folder 284)
  - Centre County Community Foundation - Broadband Internet for Rural Pennsylvania (2010-0293), 2007-2010 (Box 21, Folder 285)
  - Centre County Community Foundation - Supplemental Grant to Donor-Advised Fund (2009-0273), 2009-2013 (Box 21, Folder 286)
  - Charlotte Regional Partnership - Project Flash, Amazon (2017-55132) (Box 22, Folder 296)
  - Charlotte is Creative - Queen City Quiz Show: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52489), 2013-2016 (Box 22, Folder 297)
  - The Chicago Community Foundation - Digital Tool Development (2014-48537), 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 305)
  - The Chicago Community Foundation - On The Table Program (2015-51167), 2015-2016 (Box 22, Folder 306)
  - The Chicago Community Foundation - Second Century Project (2012-0163), 2009-2014 (Box 22, Folder 307)
  - The Chicago Community Foundation - Deep Dive 2.0 Social Labs, 2016 KCIC Reinvestment (2016-53245), 2015-2016 (Box 22, Folder 308)
  - The Chicago Community Foundation - Community Information Infrastructure (2009-0211) (Box 22, Folder 309)
  - Chris Horne - Unbox Akron: Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50680) (Box 23, Folder 314)
  - Citizen Detroit - Happy 18th Birthday! Local Citizenship Kit: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54204) (Box 23, Folder 321)
  - Citizen University - Joy of Voting (2017-53989) (Box 23, Folder 322)
  - Citizen University - Joy of Voting (2015-51757), 2015-2016 (Box 23, Folder 323)
  - City Fabrick - Place-make the Vote: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52505), 2014-2017 (Box 23, Folder 324)
  - City ID - San Jose Wayfinding Program Development (2015-50861), 2013-2015 (Box 23, Folder 325)
  - Citymart US Inc. - Demonstration Project (2014-49434), 2012-2014 (Box 24, Folder 329)
  - City of Boulder - Tree Debris to Opportunity: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52486) (Box 24, Folder 334)
  - City of Charlotte - Smart District Engagement: Neighborhood Pilot Project (2017-54490) (Box 24, Folder 335)
  - City of Charlotte - CrownTownHall: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52487) (Box 24, Folder 336)
  - City of Charlotte - Can Do Signs: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52490) (Box 24, Folder 337)
  - City of Charlotte - The Take Ten Initiative (2015-50669), 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 338)
    Support civic engagement by challenging all municipal workers to take ten minutes every week to connect with a city resident and report back on their thoughts and ideas.
  - City of Charlotte - No Barriers Project: Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50682), 2014-2015 (Box 24, Folder 339)
    To reinvigorate an underused common space between two divided Charlotte neighborhoods with light, sound, and play to stimulate community conversations and connections.
  - City of Columbus, Georgia - Urban Glen: Knight Cities Challenge (2016-52492) (Box 24, Folder 340)
  - City of Detroit - Design Center in a Box: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge (2017-54212) (Box 24, Folder 341)
  - City of Detroit - Detroit's Pink Zone: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52496) (Box 24, Folder 343)
  - City of Detroit - Give A Park, Get A Park!: A 2016 Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52497) (Box 24, Folder 344)
  - City of Duluth - Making Canal Park Pop: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54393) (Box 24, Folder 345)
  - City of Gary - City Church Ruins Garden: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54231) (Box 25, Folder 346)
  - City of Long Beach - The Outdoor Office: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2016-52504), 2016-2017 (Box 25, Folder 347)
  - City of Saint Paul - Bring Pop Up Meeting and Power to the People: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54209) (Box 25, Folder 352)
  - City of Saint Paul - 8-80 Vitality Fellow: Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50657), 2013-2015 (Box 25, Folder 353)
  - City of San Jose - Talent Attraction (2015-51718), 2015-2017 (Box 25, Folder 354)
  - City of San Jose - Fostering Civic Engagement through Service (2017-53810) (Box 25, Folder 355)
  - City of San Jose - CityDance (2017-54074) (Box 25, Folder 356)
  - City of San Jose - Update Citywide Urban Design and Historic Preservation Guidelines (2017-54083) (Box 25, Folder 357)
  - City of San Jose - City Designer for San Jose: A Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54400) (Box 25, Folder 358)
  - City of San Jose - Parks Activation and Prototyping Fund (2015-51756) (Box 25, Folder 360)
  - City of San Jose - Public Library Works (2015-51787) (Box 25, Folder 361)
  - City of San Jose - Increasing Engagement in Community Budgeting (2015-51814) (Box 26, Folder 362)
  - City of San Jose - Open Streets Planning and Pilot (2014-48620), 2013-2014 (Box 26, Folder 363)
  - City of Tallahassee - The Longest Table: Knight Cities Challenge (2016-52521) (Box 26, Folder 364)
  - City of West Palm Beach - 12 for 12: Popup to Rent: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54205) (Box 26, Folder 365)
  - Civic Incite - Civic Incite: A 2017 Knight Cities Challenge Winner (2017-54211) (Box 27, Folder 379)
    Tool to track public meetings and legislation across cities to make it easier for citizens to engage with the issues they care about.
  - Civic Nation - ALL IN Campus Democracy Challenge (2017-53892) (Box 27, Folder 380)
  - Civic Nation - Community Voting Initiative (2016-53213), 2016-2017 (Box 27, Folder 381)
  - Claire Nelson - The Urban "Consulate": Knight Cities Challenge (2015-50677) (Box 27, Folder 383)
  - The Cleveland Foundation - A 2017 Knight Community Information Lab Winner (2017-54675) (Box 27, Folder 386)
  - Coded by Kids - Philadelphia Recreation Center Programming (2017-54008) (Box 27, Folder 389)
  - Code Fever Miami, Inc. - Black Tech Week Infrastructure Development and Expansion (2016-53404), 2016-2017 (Box 27, Folder 390)
  - Code Fever Miami, Inc. - Black Tech Week (2015-51489), 2013-2016 (Box 27, Folder 391)
  - Code for America Labs, Inc. - 2015 Code for America Fellowship: Miami-Dade County (2014-49245), 2014-2015 (Box 27, Folder 392)
  - Code for America Labs, Inc. - Rewiring Government (2012-2310), 2010-2017 (Box 28, Folder 394)
  - CODeLLA.Org - Codella Scale Up (2016-53711) (Box 28, Folder 397)
  - CodeNow Inc. - CodeNow Miami (2013-45133), 2013-2015 (Box 28, Folder 398)
  - College for Creative Studies, Detroit - Igniting UNESCO City of Design Designation (2016-53262), 2015-2017 (Box 28, Folder 400)
  - The Commonwealth Institute Inc. - TCI's Women in Technology Executive Forum (2017-54878) (Box 29, Folder 408)
  - Community Development Advocates of Detroit - Partnering Community and Public Planning and Design Leadership (2016-53265) (Box 29, Folder 416)
  - Community Foundation of Central Georgia, Inc. - Macon-Bibb County Transit Study (2017-55262) (Box 29, Folder 419)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Promoting Public Dialogue on the Future of Information in Communities (2017-55047) (Box 29, Folder 420)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - New Economy Initiative 3.0 (2016-53100), 2014-2017 (Box 29, Folder 421)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - On the Table (2016-53705), 2016-2017 (Box 30, Folder 423)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Knight Nonprofit Capacity Training Stipend Program (2015-51283) (Box 30, Folder 425)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Detroit Citymart (2015-51753), 2013-2015 (Box 30, Folder 426)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - New Economy Initiative (2013-45963), 2011-2016 (Box 30, Folder 429-430)
  - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Knight Public and Nonprofit Sector Capacity Training Stipend Program (2013-47315), 2012-2013 (Box 30, Folder 431)
  - Community Foundation for the National Capital Region - Housing Preservation Tool for Tracking Rental Housing in the District of Columbia, Knight Community Information Challenge (2012-0144), 2009-2012 (Box 32, Folder 439)
  - Community Foundation of Central Georgia Inc. - Macon Action Plan Challenge (2015-51559), 2013-2017 (Box 32, Folder 442)
  - Community Foundation of Central Georgia Inc. - Macon Supplemental Grant (2009-0266), 2009-2014 (Box 32, Folder 443)
  - Community Foundation of Central Georgia Inc. - Milledgeville Supplemental Grant (2009-0267), 2008-2016 (Box 32, Folder 444)
  - Community Foundation of Grand Forks, East Grand Forks - New Flavors Food Truck: A 2016 Knight Cities Challenges Winner (2016-52501), 2013-2016 (Box 32, Folder 446)
  - Community Foundation of Greater Chattanooga, Inc. - Accessing and Using City Data, Knight Community Information Challenge (2013-46563), 2011-2013 (Box 32, Folder 447)
  - Community Foundation of Grand Forks, East Grand Forks, and Region - Online Giving Technologies (2013-46731) (Box 32, Folder 448)